rightthisminute.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy | RTM - RightThisMinute

**PLEASE READ THIS USER AGREEMENT BEFORE USING THIS SERVICE. BY CONTINUING TO USE RIGHTTHISMINUTE.COM, YOU AGREE TO ABIDE BY THE CONDITIONS OF THIS USER AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS OF THIS USER AGREEMENT, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SERVICE.**

**Personal Information**

RightThisMinute appreciates visitors to our website and your privacy is important to us. As a general policy, we do not automatically collect your personally identifiable information when you visit our Website. In certain circumstances, we may request, allow or otherwise provide you an opportunity to submit your personally identifiable information in connection with a feature, program, promotion or some other aspect of our website. Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content on our website. RightThisMinute does not collect personal information that is not provided to us. Additionally, RightThisMinute will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except when necessary to deliver a requested service. Upon request, we will provide you with the information that we maintain about you **.**

**User Content**

Any information you disclose voluntarily in content you upload or share, on RightThisMinute.com becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. We encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

**Demographic Information**

We may use aggregate data such as income, age and geography to further customize our content and enhance our services. We may share this information with advertisers and the media. Likewise, we may share this information with another company in the event that we merge, are acquired or participate in a joint venture with another company. All aggregate data will be shared without any personally identifiable information about our individual subscribers.

**Web Site Usage Information**

Likewise, we and some of our partners, may make use of cookies (small text tiles placed on your computer's hard disk by our server). They are used to collect non-personal traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This information will be used to assess how subscribers are using our services so that we may better serve you. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site. RightThisMinute does not use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

**Browser Level Information and IP Addresses**

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration when you visit our site, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system you're running, the resolution of your computer monitor, the website that referred you, and your IP address. (Your IP address is a numerical address that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you want to view) can be transmitted to you. We also use IP address information for systems administration and trouble shooting purposes. Your IP address does not tell us who you are.) **This  information is used** to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site.

**Data Collected in Connection with Ad Serving and Targeting**.

We use third-party Service Providers, such as ad networks, to serve advertising to you when you visit our Site. These Service Providers may use information about your activities while you navigate through this Site and other web sites and that they collect through cookies to provide you with advertisements about products and services that they think may be of interest to you. The information used by these Service Providers for these purposes generally does not identify you personally (in other words, the Service Providers are not using your name, address, email address, or phone number for these purposes) but it may include the IP address of your computer, browser information and time & date of visit. Data collected relates to your behavior while on this site and other websites: what ads you clicked on, what content you viewed, etc. Third parties may also gather user data and our privacy policy may not describe the privacy practices of those parties.  You can control interest-based advertising from some or all participating member companies that use HTTP cookies on your computer browser by visiting <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

**Linked Sites**

Although RightThisMinute may provide links to third party sites, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites nor do we endorse these sites. Please review each site's privacy policy to determine their use of information, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

**Advertisers**

To support our efforts we sell sponsorships of RightThisMinute mailings and on the blog to advertisers who we think you'd like to know about. These advertisers will either be identified as a Friend of RightThisMinute, Custom Mail, Advertisement, Featured Link or Sponsor.

**Public Forums**

We may offer chat rooms, blogs, message boards, bulletin boards, or similar public forums where you and other users of our website can communicate. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personal information) in connection with your use of these public forums. We may use personally identifiable and non-personal information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Website.

**Children**

The features, programs, promotions and other aspects of our website requiring the submission of personally identifiable information are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us please contact us at the e-mail address listed below. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of such child's personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof.

**Security**

RightThisMinute stores all of the information described above in restricted databases.

**Opt-out / Unsubscribe**

If we ever send you an email that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request to receive no future notices.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

RightThisMinute may change this privacy policy. Any changes will be reflected on this privacy policy page. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, you should check back at this privacy policy page periodically. WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE.

**Contact**

If you should have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@RightThisMinute.com](mailto:privacy@RightThisMinute.com) or by mail at RightThisMinute.com, 9633 S. 48th Street, Suite 185, Phoenix, AZ 85044

## RTM Favorites

###  Thrilling Overnight Challenge In Abandoned Hospital

YouTubers do some pretty wacky challenges — and all for the views. [The FAM](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCUSCuCzQIFeYe6bs20-YUdw) has decided to do something entirely crazy and we don't recommend it. He's in Miami Gardens, Florida at three in the morning about to stroll through the former Parkway West Hospital. It's a complete abandoned mess and some might even argue haunted. We could speculate it very well might be — based on the spooky things he encounters during his time there. View Now

###  Guy Embarrassed By Parents' Dancing At Baseball Game

Being on the jumbotron at a sporting event is always fun, but this guy was not having it at a recent San Diego Padres game. [KFSN](http://abc30.com/) producer Rudy Rendon tweeted out the hilarious videos of the fan getting extremely embarrassed as his mom shows off some interesting and awkward moves and his dad is laughing hard and red in the face as the dancing goes on. View Now

###  Dude Thinks Spider Is A Snack

Here's something you probably didn't expect to feel today, sympathy for a spider. When Chris and his buddies found a wolf spider, he figured that it was trying to start a fight. We think the spider was actually trying to start a web, but still, Chris decided to end the fight by...eating his opponent. Super gross and totally not cool, Chris! via [Viral Hog](https://www.facebook.com/YA.BOYY.231/videos/10216855535399647/) View Now

###  Husband Rocks At Mowing

Shelby loves it when her husband goes out to mow the lawn. He's got the moves, the boots, the hat and the attitude as he rocks out while he maintains that yard. View Now

###  Teach Us How To Fold A Fitted Sheet, Terri

The dreaded folded sheet is creating closet messes everywhere — why can't we figure it out! [Terri Metz](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCp5l87bM-Csl-VqLbyojDUA) is here to help, so no need to fear! First, you put your legs in two corners, then lay down and put your arms into the other corners, roll to one side, ease your way out, and BOOM! You're done! We love this chick's method. Honestly, it looks fun. So much fun that Gayle and Charity had to give it a try.   View Now

## Animals

###  Bear Wanders Into 'The Shining' Hotel

The [Stanley Hotel](https://www.facebook.com/thestanleyhotel/) in Estes Park, Colorado is home to a lot of scary things, but bears are not usually one of them. The famously haunted hotel that inspired Stephen King to write "The Shining" became a nice staycation destination for this black bear when it wandered into the hotel lobby. The person working the front desk was lucky to get this on camera, but then again, they've probably seen way scarier.  View Now

###  Leopard On The Hunt Right Outside Your Car!

At Pilanesberg National Park in South Africa, you can get really close to the wildlife. Like, _really_ close! Folks on safari were lucky enough to see a leopard hunting for its lunch. Despite the fact that the leopard seemed to miss out on a meal, the onlookers had a once-in-a-lifetime experience. via [Kruger National Park](https://www.youtube.com/user/exRanger7) View Now

###  Rescuers Help Whale Tangled In Fishing Nets

Thanks to an alert by a resident in San Clemente del Tuyú, Argentina, a rescue crew was quickly able to help a young humpback whale tangled in fishing nets. With 70 percent of its body out of the water, they took advantage of the low-tide — braving the brutal elements the whole way through. View Now

###  Breaking Down Walls For Doggie Rescue

Tommy the dog got himself stuck between two narrow garage walls in Russia. The heat was intense and with no food, rescuers didn't have a lot of time. Firefighters needed permission to break into one of the garages and knock out a hole in the wall to reach the pup. It took a while but the effort was certainly worth it. Now Tommy is back home and safe with his favorite human! via [Viral Video UK](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6zML4ffk7-w) View Now

###  Father And Son Embrace After Days Apart & Puppy? Best Birthday Surprise!

Time away from those you love can feel like an eternity. This can certainly be said for 53-year-old Matt and his father. Matt went to New York City for five days with his sister and although he had a great time, he couldn't wait to get back home to dad! Let's be honest, being surprised with a pet is one of life's greatest joys. Ewan Bamford would most definitely agree! Happy birthday, Ewan! View Now

###  Terrified Dog Finally Bonds With Foster Dad

When Blossom was first found, she didn't really know how to be a normal dog. The pooch was rescued from a horrifying hoarding situation, and when she first came home with foster dad Rocky Kanaka, she couldn't stop shaking and hiding. With some tender loving care from Rocky, Blossom is now thriving and happy as can be, wagging her tail everywhere! via [The Dodo](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCINb0wqPz-A0dV9nARjJlOQ) View Now

###  Bird Enthusiasts Flock To Vancouver For Week-Long Festival

Have you ever fantasized about being a bird? Come on, don't lie. These bird-lovers are living their truth at the first ever [Vancouver International Bird Festival](http://www.vanbirdfest.com/). The event brings enthusiasts from all over to dress up and celebrate their winged friends. It's a week-long event that kicks off with a parade, and is followed by a week of "bird-related activities," which include bird tours, exhibits and lectures by ornithologists! This festival runs from Aug. 19 to Aug. 26, so check it out if you're in the area! It'll be a HOOT. View Now

###  Take Your Safari Elsewhere!

We've seen it before — the animals of South Africa aren't always in the mood for tourists or safari vehicles. In this buffalo's case, it certainly was not having any kind of tourist activity. The animal repeatedly rams into the open-sided vehicle until the guide is safely able to drive away. View Now
